It means that it's as if there was already a potential that
这意味着好像已经有一个潜力
was about to be born, green.
即将诞生，绿色。
Do you understand?
你们明白吗？
It's the form field.
这是形态场。
So, that is to say, there isn't yet,
所以也就是说还没有，
it is said to be an expression that defines a hypothetical field
我们说这是一个定义了假设场的表达
that would contain energy without matter.
它包含没有物质的能量。
This is already a bit more complex.
这已经有点复杂了。
And that's where it will happen.
这就是它将发生的地方。
We've seen the impact down to the nucleus level,
我们看到了直到细胞核层面的影响，
tensegrity,
张拉整体，
the importance of the matrix here.
这里基质的重要性。
We've seen all the mechanisms,
我们看到了所有机制，
that it's not just an electromagnetic field,
这不仅仅是一个电磁场，
but temperature, heat, mechanical stresses,
还有温度、热量、机械应力，
hydrostatic pressures, electric fields,
静水压力、电场，
redox systems.
氧化还原系统。
All of this will play a role in the system's homeostasis.
所有这些都将在系统的稳态中发挥作用。
The presence of elementary particles
基本粒子的存在
with the concept of electromagnetic energy.
伴随着电磁能量的概念。
The polarized human, electromagnetic field,
极化的人，电磁场，
Maxwell's law.
麦克斯韦定律。
There is the notion of space and time.
还有空间和时间的概念。
There's even more, there's light.
还有更多，还有光。
We'll just do that.
我们就做这个。
I have many of these lines.
我有很多这样的线条。
I have a cluster of cells
我有一堆细胞
what makes it so
是什么导致
that it will differentiate
它会分化
we saw that there were changes
我们看到有变化
and this ulnar stress
尺骨的这种应力
it's all about mechanotransduction
这就是完整的机械转导过程
I'm shedding a lot of light
我着重阐明
I modify my parameter
我调整我的参数
when I have an electric field
当存在电场时
what do I have?
我们会得到什么呢？
I always have an electromagnetic field
总是会有一个电磁场
and this allows
这便使得
the system to have cohesion
系统能够保持内聚性
But furthermore, I have a reference, meaning that the cell
但此外，我们还有一个参照，这意味着细胞
that is here, compared to the cell that is here, does not have the
位于此处的，相对于位于彼处的细胞，不具备
same reference in relation to the space in which it is defined.
相同的参照，相对于其所界定的空间
This means that the heritage that is here will express itself differently
这意味着此处的遗传物质将以不同的方式表达
at a given moment than the heritage that is here.
与彼处的遗传物质在特定时刻有所不同
Even if initially, all cells seem.
即使最初，所有细胞看起来
to have the same heritage.
具有相同的遗传物质
These are layers
这些是细胞层
that will be able to express themselves
它们将能够表达自身
in different spaces and times
在不同的空间和时间中
depending on the chronology
根据时间顺序的不同
and the location in which
以及它们所处的具体位置
they are found in relation to the midline
相对于中线
and the electric field.
和电场
Do you understand?
你们明白吗？
It's the position that
这是你所处的
you have in relation
相对于
to this electromagnetic field.
这个电磁场的位置
Which will release the information.
它将释放信息
Among others.
除此之外
It's the CDI.
这是CDI
several parameters are involved
有几个参数会起作用
but already, this is the first major component
但这已经是第一个主要组成部分
very important
非常重要
whence comes polarity
极性从何而来
whence come these forces
这些力从何而来
they were present long before us
它们在我们之前就存在了
they are still present long after us
它们在我们之后仍将存在
simply
只是
the energy of matter
物质能量
concentrated vibratory
集中振动
light induces matter
光诱导物质
the fluid, electricity
流体，电力
the fluid and densification
流体和致密化
and then at a given moment, it restarts
然后，在某个时刻它又重新开始
and we
然后我们
We observe what causes, all of a sudden, one cell to become hepatic
我们看到为什么突然间，一个细胞会变成肝细胞
and another to become cerebral.
而另一个会变成脑细胞。
This is based on relocation in space and time.
这是根据在空间和时间上的重新定位。
Sometimes, one can take cell lineages and deposit them there.
有时候，我们可以取一些细胞系束并将其放置在那里。
They can change again.
它们可以再次改变。
Sometimes, they no longer can, depending on time.
有时候，它们不能再改变，这取决于时间。
You now have a clear image of the difference between an epithelial tissue
你们现在对上皮组织和
and a connective tissue.
结缔组织之间的区别有了清晰的认识。
It could serve.
它可能是。
the difference between an ecto, endo, meso tissue, so I will give you a
外胚层、内胚层、中胚层组织之间的区别，那么我将给你们一个
tissue,
组织，
I don't know, something, you will just tell me what it is, okay,
我不知道，某种东西，你们只需告诉我那是什么，好吗，
the tongue, the
舌头，
tongue, endo, dorsally, it's digestive,
舌头，内胚层，在背部，是消化系统，
I think there will still be a muscle, the interior, yes, c
我认为仍然会有肌肉，内部，是的，这
it's a mixture,
这是一个混合体，
of endo, the epithelial tissue
内胚层来源的，上皮组织
is endo, the tissue
是内胚层来源的，组织
muscular is meso.
肌肉组织是中胚层来源的。
The pancreas.
胰腺。
But it's endo.
但它是内胚层来源的。
So everything that is hormonal
所以所有与激素相关的
derives from epithelial tissue,
都源自上皮组织，
from boundary tissue.
即界限组织。
That means all glands
这意味着所有腺体，
exocrine, endocrine, etc.
外分泌腺、内分泌腺等，
always come
都始终源自
from epithelial tissue. In other words,
上皮组织。换句话说，
they always come from boundary tissue.
它们始终源自界限组织。
other words, they always derive from the ectoderm
换句话说，它们始终源自外胚层
or from the endoderm.
或内胚层。
Never from the mesoderm.
绝非中胚层。
That was important too, now that we have the colors.
这一点也很重要，现在我们有了这些颜色（指胚层区分）。
and the cranial base is a balance
而颅底是
between my neurocranium and my viscerocranium.
我的神经颅和脏颅之间的平衡。
I will derive
我将推导
the tissues. In the first three
这些组织。在最初的三个
weeks,
星期内，
beginning of the third week,
第三周初期，
we already have something truly formed.
我们已经真正完成了一些事情。
So we can divide
所以我们可以将
into three main parts, the period
胚胎发育期分为三个主要阶段，即
known as embryogenesis,
胚胎形成期，
the period known as organogenesis
器官形成期，
and the period known as the period
以及胎儿期。
fetal. In two months,
胎儿期。在两个月内,
all structures,
所有结构,
two, three months, all my noble structures
两到三个月时，所有重要的结构
will already be formed. Afterwards, it's
将已经形成。之后，就是
maturation, growth.
成熟和生长。
I strongly emphasize here the notion
我在这里非常强调
of growth, that
生长这个概念，即
motility, it's a movement
动度，它是一种运动
that is always present in the body,
始终存在于身体中,
and which will be defined by a developmental system.
并将由一个发育系统来定义。
It's a movement as we've seen, except that it becomes more complex in different tissues.
这是一种我们已经看到的运动，只是它在不同组织中变得复杂。
Growth and gametogenesis, we start there.
生长和配子发生，我们从这里开始。